[
  {
    "episode": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Welcome to Season _ of NBA 2KTV",
        "answer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "The MyCAREER Story in NBA 2K26 is called",
        "answer": "Out of Bounds"
      },
      {
        "question": "In NBA 2K26, you and up to 50 people can earn rewards in _.",
        "answer": "Crews"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which WNBA Player Starts NBA 2K26 with the highest overall rating?",
        "answer": "Napheesa Collier"
      },
      {
        "question": "In NBA 2K26, which attribute category will you specialize in the most?",
        "answer": "Any"
      },
      {
        "question": "WNBA Player Card can now join your lineup in which mode?",
        "answer": "MyTEAM"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which MyTEAM mode features a 4-point line?",
        "answer": "Clutch-Time"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which MyTEAM mode has its own building in The City",
        "answer": "Triple Threat Park"
      },
      {
        "question": "In NBA 2K26, the Max Height for a MyPLAYER is now 7'4â€³",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the MyCAREER Reward for reaching level 40 in Season 1?",
        "answer": "+1 Cap Breaker"
      },
      {
        "question": "What position will you make your first MyPLAYER Build?",
        "answer": "Any"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which badge increases your ability to intercept opposing passes?",
        "answer": "Interceptor"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which badge extends your three-point shooting range",
        "answer": "Limitless Range"
      },
      {
        "question": "In every season of NBA 2K26, there are _ levels of prizes to earn",
        "answer": "40"
      },
      {
        "question": "What hashtag do you need to use when submitting plays to 2KTV?",
        "answer": "#2KTVWOW"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the cover athlete for the NBA 2K26 Superstar Edition?",
        "answer": "Carmelo Anthony"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team won the NBA 2K26 Summer League Championship?",
        "answer": "Charlotte Hornets"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "episode": 2,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "The Theater hosts _ weekly game modes that change every Friday.",
        "answer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "In the 2K26 MyCareer story, you can play for teams in Spain or _.",
        "answer": "France"
      },
      {
        "question": "In MyCareer, you can earn badges in _ tiers.",
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "It is possible to use a Cap Breaker for more than a +1 attribute boost.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "The earliest you can earn Rebirths is when you reach this Overall Rating.",
        "answer": "90"
      },
      {
        "question": "Holding _ before receiving a pass speeds up your shot release.",
        "answer": "Left Trigger"
      },
      {
        "question": "Applying _ raises a badge by 1 level in clutch moments.",
        "answer": "Clutch Gene"
      },
      {
        "question": "You can exchange Hidden Gems cards for a new series called _.",
        "answer": "Wild Gems"
      },
      {
        "question": "September _ marks the return of the King of the Court in MyTEAM.",
        "answer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "In NBA 2K26, you can now play Salary Cap online or _.",
        "answer": "Single Player"
      },
      {
        "question": "The Gatorade RX Bottle provides a _ MyPoints boost for workouts.",
        "answer": "20%"
      }
    ]
  }
]
